

CONTACT INFO

+2348131649892

sanyaoluadefemi@gmail.com

www.mywebsite.com

in linkedin.com/femi sanyaolu

Yoruba, English

EDUCATION

2015 - 2019

Bsc. Library and Information Science

Tai Solarin University of Education

LANGUAGES

English

Yoruba

OTHER SKILLS

Frontend Development

Digital Marketing

Customer Relationship Mngt.

Microsoft Office Suite

Computer Networking

Emotional Intelligence

INTEREST

Reading

Adventure

Traveling

Surfing the Internet

PROFILE

Solution driven Web Developer, adept at contributing to highly collaboratively work environment, finding solutions and determining customer satisfaction. Proven experience developing consumer focused websites using HTML, CSS (Bootstrap, tailwindcss), and JavaScript (jquery, Ajax, React.js, Redux). Meeting highest standards for web design, user experience, best practices and speed. Designed and developed web application across multiple APIs, third party integrations and databases.

EXPERIENCE

April 2020 - Present Devcent Technology

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER (REACT.JS)

Developed designs to meet specific requirements such as quick-loading sites with particular layouts.

Employed coding practices based on commonly accepted standards to establish site layout and user interface

December 2020 - Present Educrest Institute

FRONTEND DEVELOPER (FREELANCER)

Assisted web presence planning, implementing changes and integrating requested elements to streamline business operations.

Generated web hosting presence to accommodate specified needs, uploading and maintaining files on account.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

